

YEHOR BOICHENKO

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I'm a junior front-end developer with a desire to learn and growth with a collaborative team environment. I have a good knowledge of HTML, CSS/SASS, JavaScript and React. Also, I have hands-on experience in following Agile/ Scrum methodology when I'm working in a team. Eager learner, responsible guy who will never put tasks on the back burner.

CONTACTS

Kyiv, Ukraine +380663053171 boichenko.yehor@gmail.com https://github.com/YehorBoichenko

TECH SKILLS

- HTML5/CSS3/SASS
- JavaScript
- -TypeScript
- React.js
- Material UI
- Axios
- Lodash
- Styled components

SOFT SKILLS

- Articulate
- Enthusiastic
- Multitasking
- Cooperative
- Attentive

LANGUAGES

English -Advanced Ukrainian - Native Russian - Native German - Intermediate

PERSONAL PROJECTS:

• <u>Web studio</u>, <u>Link</u> (HTML5/SASS/CSS/Parcel/Adaptive design) Description: Multi-page web application created for web studio.

• Gym, Link (HTML5/SASS/CSS/Adaptive design/API)

Description: Landing page created for sports club.

• Image finder, Link (React/API/CSS/HTML)

Simple web app with open API for searching images.

TEAM PROJECTS:

• Hellish English, Link (HTML5/SASS/Adaptive design)

Adaptive website for the English language school.

Role: technical-lead (developed header, footer modal windows, bugfix)

<u>Filmoteka</u>, <u>Link</u> (Html5/SASS/ Javascript/RestAPI,AJAX)

Web application developed for searching and monitoring upcoming releases. Role: Front-end developer. (Developed theme switcher, header, footer, modal window and working with local storage)

• KapustaApp, Link (Html5/CSS/ReactJS/RestAPI)

Web application developed for calculating income and expenses.

Role: Front-end developer. (Developed homepage, routes, modal windows and worked with Chart.js)

WORK EXPERIENCE

LOGISTIC DISPATCHER AT LIGHT ROAD LLC

September 2021 - January 2022 | Ukraine

- Communicating with brokers and drivers through calls or live chats.
- Provide time-critical updates to broker and client.
- Lead drivers and monitor the route, updating status as needed.

CUSTOMER SUPPORT SPECIALIST AT U.S. LEGACY

June 2020 - August 2021 | Ukraine

- Accept and dispatch maintenance requests from home leasing companies and homeowners.
- Direct and monitor daily assignments. Assign work and schedule technicians to ensure all maintenance requests are dispatched in a timely fashion.
- -Handle customer concerns and requests for information in an expeditious and professional manner.

Education

IT SCHOOL GOIT | KYIV, UKRAINE

Mar 2022 - Sept 2022

Full stack Front-end developer

V.I.VERNADSKIY TAURIDA NATIONAL UNIVERSITY | KYIV

Philology

Bachelor's degree (with honor):

- ·September 2016-June 2020 | Germanic group of languages and literature (translation inclusive)
- · Master's degree:

·September 2020 - January 2022 | Secondary education (English language and literature)